[
    {
        "question": "sample question1",
        "words": {
          "4": "BCPword4",
          "1": "BCPword1",
          "3": "BCPword3",
          "2": "BCPword2",
          "5": "BCPword5",
          "6": "BCPword6",
          "7": "BCPword7",
          "8": "BCPword8"
        },
        "answers":[[1,3,4,2],[4,2,1,3]]
    },
    {
        "question": "sample question2",
        "words": {
          "4": "BCPword4",
          "1": "BCPword1",
          "3": "BCPword3",
          "2": "BCPword2",
          "5": "BCPword5",
          "6": "BCPword6",
          "7": "BCPword7",
          "8": "BCPword8"
        },
        "answers":[[7,3,2,5],[8,2,6,1,3],[2,5,6]]
    },
    {
        "question": "sample question1",
        "words": {
          "4": "BCPword4",
          "1": "BCPword1",
          "3": "BCPword3",
          "2": "BCPword2",
          "5": "BCPword5",
          "6": "BCPword6",
          "7": "BCPword7",
          "8": "BCPword8"
        },
        "answers":[[1,3,4,2],[4,2,1,3]]
    },
    {
        "question": "sample question2",
        "words": {
          "4": "BCPword4",
          "1": "BCPword1",
          "3": "BCPword3",
          "2": "BCPword2",
          "5": "BCPword5",
          "6": "BCPword6",
          "7": "BCPword7",
          "8": "BCPword8"
        },
        "answers":[[7,3,2,5],[8,2,6,1,3],[2,5,6]]
    },
    {
        "question": "sample question1",
        "words": {
          "4": "BCPword4",
          "1": "BCPword1",
          "3": "BCPword3",
          "2": "BCPword2",
          "5": "BCPword5",
          "6": "BCPword6",
          "7": "BCPword7",
          "8": "BCPword8"
        },
        "answers":[[1,3,4,2],[4,2,1,3]]
    },
    {
        "question": "sample question2",
        "words": {
          "4": "BCPword4",
          "1": "BCPword1",
          "3": "BCPword3",
          "2": "BCPword2",
          "5": "BCPword5",
          "6": "BCPword6",
          "7": "BCPword7",
          "8": "BCPword8"
        },
        "answers":[[7,3,2,5],[8,2,6,1,3],[2,5,6]]
    },
    {
        "question": "sample question1",
        "words": {
          "4": "BCPword4",
          "1": "BCPword1",
          "3": "BCPword3",
          "2": "BCPword2",
          "5": "BCPword5",
          "6": "BCPword6",
          "7": "BCPword7",
          "8": "BCPword8"
        },
        "answers":[[1,3,4,2],[4,2,1,3]]
    },
    {
        "question": "sample question2",
        "words": {
          "4": "BCPword4",
          "1": "BCPword1",
          "3": "BCPword3",
          "2": "BCPword2",
          "5": "BCPword5",
          "6": "BCPword6",
          "7": "BCPword7",
          "8": "BCPword8"
        },
        "answers":[[7,3,2,5],[8,2,6,1,3],[2,5,6]]
    },
    {
        "question": "sample question1",
        "words": {
          "4": "BCPword4",
          "1": "BCPword1",
          "3": "BCPword3",
          "2": "BCPword2",
          "5": "BCPword5",
          "6": "BCPword6",
          "7": "BCPword7",
          "8": "BCPword8"
        },
        "answers":[[1,3,4,2],[4,2,1,3]]
    },
    {
        "question": "sample question2",
        "words": {
          "4": "BCPword4",
          "1": "BCPword1",
          "3": "BCPword3",
          "2": "BCPword2",
          "5": "BCPword5",
          "6": "BCPword6",
          "7": "BCPword7",
          "8": "BCPword8"
        },
        "answers":[[7,3,2,5],[8,2,6,1,3],[2,5,6]]
    },
    {
        "question": "sample question1",
        "words": {
          "4": "BCPword4",
          "1": "BCPword1",
          "3": "BCPword3",
          "2": "BCPword2",
          "5": "BCPword5",
          "6": "BCPword6",
          "7": "BCPword7",
          "8": "BCPword8"
        },
        "answers":[[1,3,4,2],[4,2,1,3]]
    },
    {
        "question": "sample question2",
        "words": {
          "4": "BCPword4",
          "1": "BCPword1",
          "3": "BCPword3",
          "2": "BCPword2",
          "5": "BCPword5",
          "6": "BCPword6",
          "7": "BCPword7",
          "8": "BCPword8"
        },
        "answers":[[7,3,2,5],[8,2,6,1,3],[2,5,6]]
    }
]
